poiseandpurpose.com 2016-10-23

# Poise & Purpose Privacy Statement

Updated: February 1, 2015

Welcome to Poise and Purpose! This Privacy Statement explains the information practices on our website, Poise and Purpose

Information Collection

When you visit our Site, we may collect certain personal information you knowingly choose to disclose to us, such as your name and email address. You may provide this information when you register with the Site, participate in promotions or surveys, or agree to receive messages from Poise and Purpose. The Site may also passively collect non-personal information that is automatically sent to us by your web browser or device.

We may also collect aggregated information as you visit the Site.

### Information Use

We may use the information we collect from you, your browser or device to:

  * send promotional messages from Poise and Purpose or similar companies to you;
  * respond to your requests;
  * confirm your registration with the Site;
  * analyze preferences, trends, and statistics;
  * operate the Site and customize your experience;
  * identify or remedy potential threats to the Site’s security; and
  * for any other purpose stated at the time of collection.

### Cookies

This Site is cookie-enabled to give you a more customized user experience. A cookie is a small piece of information that a website can store on a computer and later use to recognize a user. A purpose of cookies is to enhance your ability to receive the information you want. We use two types of cookies to enhance the experience of users: session cookies and persistent cookies. A session cookie expires when a user closes the browser in which this website was viewed. A persistent cookie expires on a pre-determined date. Users can personalize their browser settings to reject cookies, although certain features of the Site may not function as intended.

### Information We Collect When You Interact With Third-Party Sites

The Site may include functionality that allows certain kinds of interactions between the Site and your account on a third-party web site or application. The use of this functionality may involve the third-party site providing information, including Personal Information, to us. For example, we may provide links on the Site to facilitate sending Tweets or Facebook, Instagram, Pinterest or Google+ postings. These third parties may retain any information used or provided in any such communications or activities and these third parties’ practices are not subject to our Privacy Statement. Further, when you use third-party sites or services, you are using their services and not our services and they, not we, are responsible for their practices. You should review the applicable third-party privacy policies before using such third-party tools on our Site.

### Sharing Information

Poise and Purpose may share your personal information, including your name and email address with third parties, such as affiliates, advertising partners, and unaffiliated third parties whose products and services Poise and Purpose thinks you may enjoy. Some of these third parties may use your personal information for marketing purposes.

If we or some or all of our assets are acquired by another organization, including through bankruptcy, that organization will possess the information collected by us, and it will assume the rights and obligations regarding your information as described in this Privacy Statement.

We may disclose personal information or other data to comply with law or legal requirements, enforce or apply our Terms of Service and other agreements, or protect our rights, property, or safety of our users, or others.

### Third Party Links

For your convenience, this Site may contain certain hyperlinks to other websites. We make no promises or guarantees regarding data collection on the hyperlinked pages that are not operated by

Poise and Purpose. We recommend that you read the privacy policy/statement for each site you visit.

### Your Choices

We may use the personal information we collect from you to provide you with opportunities to offer you products and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like to opt out of future promotional materials from us, you may indicate this preference by following the unsubscribe instructions at the end of such email communications or by contacting us at poiseandpurposesite@gmail.com. If you would no longer like to receive offers from our marketing partners, you can unsubscribe by following the unsubscribe link located at the bottom of each email communication.

### Interest Based Advertising

We may partner with third-party advertising providers to serve ads on our behalf on non-affiliated third party sites. Some of those ads may be personalized, meaning that they are intended to be relevant to you based on information we or the online advertising network serving the ad collect about your online activities here and elsewhere over time. For example, anonymous information collected across multiple sites that you visit over time may enable the ad network to predict your preferences and show you ads that are most likely to be of interest to you. Please note that we do not share any information that identifies you personally with the third party service providers who serve ads on our behalf.

To opt out of these types of ads, please visit the Network Advertising Initiative for information about how to opt-out of interest-based advertising by their members. See [networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/) for general information about the NAI and you can [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp) for the opt-out page. You may also visit [aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/consumers/) to learn about online behavioral advertising and how to opt-out from online behavioral ads served by some or all participating companies.

### Your California Privacy Rights

As described in this Privacy Statement, from time to time we may make your personal information available to third parties for their marketing purposes. If you do not want us to share your personal information with third parties, you may opt-out of this information sharing by emailing us at [poiseandpurposesite](mailto:\[contact_email\])@gmail.com.

### Updates

From time to time, we may update this Privacy Statement. We will notify you of any material changes to our Privacy Statement by updating this page. We encourage you periodically to check this Site to learn about the information we collect, use, and share. Your continued use of the Site affirms your agreement to such changes.

### Contact Us

Please contact us if you have questions about our Privacy Statement at poiseandpurposesite@gmail.com.
